// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who was the BEST known for making the thought of evolution acceptable for scientists in the 19th century?",
    answer: "B. Charles Darwin",
    options: [
      "A. Alfred Wallace",
      "B. Charles Darwin",
      "C. James Hutton",
      "D. All the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who developed the theory of evolution by natural selection?",
    answer: "A. Charles Darwin and Alfred Wallace",
    options: [
      "A. Charles Darwin and Alfred Wallace",
      "B. Charles Lyell and Charles Darwin",
      "C. Charles Lyell and James Hutton",
      "D. Erasmus Darwin and Lamarck",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which phrase BEST defines evolution by natural selection?",
    answer: "D. A process of change in species over time",
    options: [
      "A. Changes during a species because it becomes more perfect",
      "B. A sudden replacement of one population by another",
      "C. An adaptation of a species to its environment",
      "D. A process of change in species over time",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following BEST describes a phylogenetic tree that is ʺrootedʺ?",
    answer: "B. At whose base is found the common ancestor of all taxa depicted thereon tree.",
    options: [
      "A. It indicates our uncertainty about the evolutionary relationships of the taxa depicted on the tree.",
      "B. At whose base is found the common ancestor of all taxa depicted thereon tree.",
      "C. It illustrates the rampant gene swapping that occurred early in life’s history",
      "D. It extends back to the origin of life on Earth.",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following is NOT an example of physical adaptations traits by natural selection?",
    answer: "C. Migration",
    options: [
      "A. Color",
      "B. Camouflage",
      "C. Migration",
      "D. Mimicry",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following pair is BEST example of homologous structures?",
    answer: "A. bat forelimb and bird wing",
    options: [
      "A. bat forelimb and bird wing",
      "B. bat wing and human hand",
      "C. owl wing and hornet wing",
      "D. porcupine quill and cactus spine",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following pair is an example of analogous structure?",
    answer: "D. bat and bird wings",
    options: [
      "A. front flippers of whales and forelegs of dog",
      "B. grasshopper leg and the sea star arm",
      "C. tail of monkeys and cats",
      "D. bat and bird wings",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "When using a cladistic approach to systematics, which of the following is considered MOST important for classification?",
    answer: "D. shared derived characters",
    options: [
      "A. analogous primitive characters",
      "B. the number of homoplasies",
      "C. shared primitive characters",
      "D. shared derived characters",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which pair is an example of homologous structure?",
    answer: "D. bird and bat wing",
    options: [
      "A. front flippers of whales and forelegs of dog",
      "B. grasshopper leg and the sea star arm",
      "C. dragon fly wing and butterfly wing",
      "D. bird and bat wing",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following result in the change of DNA sequence?",
    answer: "C. Mutation",
    options: [
      "A. Genetic drift",
      "B. Migration",
      "C. Mutation",
      "D. Natural selection",
    ],
  },
];
